Jonathan Horst

3752 24th Street San Francisco CA 94114 415.317.2140 (mobile) - JonathanHorst13@Gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Highly motivated individual committed to realizing personal and organizational goals through excellence, teamwork, and a drive to do whatever it takes. Strong desire to be of service to and positively affect the lives of others. Continually striving to improve myself and approach every experience as an opportunity for growth.

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Extraordinary Organizational Abilities - Highly organized and detail oriented.

Excellent Time-Management Skills - Able to handle multiple tasks at once and prioritize.

Outstanding Interpersonal Communication – Work with a wide variety of individuals in an amiable and professional manner.

Demonstrated Leadership Qualities – Driven to contribute to the success of others through collaboration and coaching.

Very Positive and Optimistic Mindset – Approach every challenge as an opportunity for growth and improvement.

Strong Working Knowledge of IT – Microsoft Office Word, Excel, PowerPoint, etc; as well as various accounting software applications including QuickBooks, ProSystems Fx.

QUALIFICATIONS SUMMARY

2 % years experience in financial planning – Built a practice as an entrepreneur; marketing to desired target markets; relating complex financial concepts to clients; interviewing, training, motivating, and collaborating with colleagues; analyzing clients' financial wellness and proposing recommendations to achieve goals.

4 years of public accounting experience – Auditing, bookkeeping, preparing financial statements and reports, payroll, business valuation, benefit plan administration, tax preparation; articulating complex regulations, financial concepts, and laws to clients.

Trustee experience – Served organizations in an executive role and other positions to contribute to community and to be of service to others.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Series 7 & Series 66 Licenses
- Life, Health, Disability, and Long-Term Care Licenses in Colorado

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Registered Client Service Associate

Morgan Stanley Smith Barney

01.2012 – 04.2012San Francisco, California

Pastry Chef

Dalvay by the Sea Resort

05.2011 – 06.2011Prince Edward Island, Canada

Financial Advisor

Waddell & Reed

Bondi & Co LLC

07.2008 – 06.2010 *Denver, Colorado*

Auditor

01.2008 – 05.2008 *Denver, Colorado*

Bookkeeper	07.2007 - 12.2007
Well-Balanced Accounting Inc	Denver, Colorado
Accountant	05.2006 - 07.2007
Zick Business Advisors Inc	Denver, Colorado
ZICK DUSINESS AUVISORS THE	Deliver, Colorado
Accountant	01.2006 - 05.2006
Terry & Stephenson	Denver, Colorado
, ,	,
Bookkeeper	04.2004 - 01.2006
Well-Balanced Accounting Inc	Denver, Colorado
COMMUNITY SERVICE	
Treasurer	11.2009 - 06.2010
Denver Professional Men's Club	Denver, Colorado
Co-Chair (UR 2)	07.2009 - 06.2010
Human Rights Campaign (HRC) Colorado	Denver, Colorado
Tuanannan	10 2000 02 2010
Treasurer	10.2009 - 03.2010
The Alexander Foundation	Denver, Colorado
Vice-President	09.2009 - 01.2010
Denver Metro Chamber of Commerce Group	Denver, Colorado
Deliver Metro Chamber of Commerce Group	Deliver, Colorado
Volunteer	04.2005 - 04.2007
Community Sailing of Colorado	Denver, Colorado
, <u>-</u>	,
Volunteer	10.2006 - 11.2006
Children's Museum of Denver	Denver, Colorado
Treasurer	08.2005 - 05.2006
Beta Alpha Psi	Denver, Colorado
EDUCATION LICTORY	
EDUCATION HISTORY	
Pastry Arts Certificate	09.2010 - 04.2011
Culinary Institute of Canada	Prince Edward Island, Canada
Bachelors – Triple Major: Finance, Accounting, & German	01.2000 - 05.2006
University of Colorado	
University of Colorado	Denver, Colorado
LANGUAGES	
English (First language) German	
Linguisti (i inscranigaage)	
INTERESTS & HOBBIES	

INTERESTS & HOBBIES

Yoga, Meditation, Cooking, Tennis, Fencing, Cycling, Hiking, Climbing, Personal Development

REFERENCES

Dave Shimko	Mary Jo Houser	Zach Bouck
Admissions Counselor	Bookkeeper & Owner	District Manager
Ashford University	Well-Balanced Accounting Inc	Waddell & Reed
866.974.5700 x6680	303.692.8363	702.261.5379
Renaldo Phillips	George Ira Carroll	Anna Lovascio-Hansen
CEO	Life Coach	Internal Auditor
Vertu Foundation	Inner Resonant Awareness	City & County of Denver
303.489.5457	303.991.4680	720.913.5064